trustlink.org 2011-05-26

# Privacy Policy

Interested in a company?   
Search for a company to find out what other TrustLinkers have to say about their experiences. Did they have good or bad experiences? How many other people feel the same way? These questions, along with many others, could be answered when you view the information we have on a company. If you feel compelled to post your own two cents, please do so by posting a review.

TrustLink Privacy Policy  
---  
TrustLink is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online.  
   
TrustLink's Commitment to Online Security  
Physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. Billing information is encrypted whenever transmitted or received online. Personal information is used by staff, volunteers and other designated personnel. All TrustLink agents and contractors with access to personal information obtained on the TrustLink web site will also abide by this policy.  
   
Personal Information that TrustLink May Collect Online  
TrustLink collects the following types of personal information: names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and facsimile numbers, billing information, and complaint information. TrustLink may also collect business information from sole proprietorships and partnerships that apply for program participation, some of which might constitute personal information, as well as personal information from individuals.  
   
TrustLink will not knowingly collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 13, and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.   
   
How TrustLink May Use Personal Information Collected Online  
TrustLink will not use your personal information other than for the purpose for which it was submitted without your consent. We use personal information to reply to inquiries and to warn the public about questionable business practices. In that regard, we may share the information with the media or government agencies. We also process business and billing requests related to program participation. At certain points where personal information is collected on our site, there may be a box where you may indicate you would like to be on a list to receive information about other TrustLink programs and services and about ways to support TrustLink. At any time you can add or remove your name from our mailing list by contacting us at [privacy@trustlink.org]().  
   
How Your Information May Be Shared  
We will release personal information to appropriate parties under the following circumstances:  

Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate  
If your personal information changes, please email us at [privacy@trustlink.org](mailto:privacy@trustlink.org) with the new information, and, if appropriate, we will change your records. Let us also know the department that led your submission of personal information so we may efficiently locate your information.  
   
Computer Tracking and Cookies  
Our web site is not set up to track, collect, or distribute personal information not entered by its visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our site. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.  
   
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. TrustLink uses cookies to provide easier site navigation and access. You can still use the TrustLink site if your browser is set to reject cookies.  
   
Problems  
If you have a complaint about TrustLink's compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us at [privacy@trustlink.org](mailto:privacy@trustlink.org).
